In this clip we're going to talk about how to buy a trophy. Most people will come into my show room and they'll ask me how much is a twenty inch trophy.
And I say to them we don't sell trophies by the inch, and I give them this fine example here.
This is a forty-eight inch trophy.
If you go to any trophy store and they can offer you this forty-eight inch trophy for as little as $20.
As you can see, if you were to buy a trophy by the inch, someone could sell you this and you wouldn't be very happy with it.
So my recommendation is not to try and buy a trophy based on how tall it is but take into consideration the materials that it's made of.
We use marble bases that are imported directly from Italy.
We also put little felt dots on the bottom of the trophies and that keeps them from scratching your furniture when you get home.
A lot of times people will try and save money in building a trophy by leaving out these little things.
So when it comes to buying a trophy, it's not how tall it is for the dollar.
It's really, what you get for your dollar.